* Log into your IDW.community account

Privacy Policy
==============

We understand that your privacy is very important to you. That's why we've developed this policy to ensure that your privacy is protected while using our sites.

About IDW.community and Information We Collect

We're an online network which provides you useful tools and communities to post and respond to questions. IDW.community is FREE.  
  
In our online anonymous registration form, we may ask you to provide us with certain information such as your email address and an initial question. None of your personally identifiable information can be accessed or used by the public to identify a specific individual. While using the website, we save your posts and comments as well as some of the pages that you view.  
  
That being said, some users may elect to connect their account on IDW.community to third-party sites such as Facebook or Google. In these cases, a user's profile name, email and sometimes main photo is collected but not shown.

Our Use of Your Information

We internally use personally identifiable information of our users to improve our marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor your online experience to meet your needs.  
  
We also send periodic informational updates to our members via email.  
  
We use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement.  

Our Disclosure of Your Information

We DO NOT sell, rent, or give any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission.  
  
In order to maintain a healthy community, IDW.community cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights.

Your use of Other Users' Information

IDW.community and our users do not tolerate spam, harassment, or threats.

Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information

Once you register, you will be able to review and change much of your personally identifiable information at IDW.community including:

* Your email address
* Your city, state, zip code, country
* Your password
* Your profile

Questions and answers, once posted, cannot be changed but you can remove any public postings by logging in and clicking on the "Delete" button next to your posts.

Security

IDW.community has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. IDW.community uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information such as firewalls. However, please not that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. For extra layers of protection of your identity online, in general, we suggest not using personally identifiable email addresses and not using the same passwords across multiple web sites.

Email This Page to a Friend/Invite Friends Services

The terms applicable to the Email This Profile to a Friend or Invite Friends services apply to your use of that service. Without limiting the foregoing, you may not use the service to send spam.

* Copyright © 2024 IDW.community - All rights reserved.

* IDW.community is a community for fans of the Intellectual Dark Web! We're non-commercial, fan-operated, and independent of any public figure.

[](javascript:void(0);)
